Guide to the Ithaca City of Asylum records, 2001-2016.
Ithaca City of Asylum records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Ithaca City of Asylum records, 2001-2016.
8469
Ithaca City of Asylum.
.4 cubic feet.
Correspondence, newspapers, reports, photographs, manuscripts.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, board meeting minutes, annual reports, newspaper clippings, photographs, and the creative work of writers-in-residence.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Ithaca City of Asylum assists visiting writers and their families and is a project of the Center for Transformative Action, a non-profit organization affiliated with Cornell University, Ithaca College and Wells College.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, board meeting minutes, annual reports, newspaper clippings, photographs, and the creative work of writers-in-residence.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Ithaca City of Asylum.; Cornell University.; Cornell Universtiy. Center for Transformative Action.; Ithaca College.; Wells College.
Subjects:
Creative writing (Higher education) -- Study and teaching -- North America
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Founding Documents, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Board Meeting Records, 2001-2013 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Budgets, 2001-2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Grants and Fundraising, 2001-2013 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Annual Reports, 2010-2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Publicity, 2001-2013 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Related Organizations, 2001-2014 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Photographs, 2001-2014 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Expectations for Writers, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Yi-Ping Personal and Business Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Yi-Ping Creative Work, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Yi-Ping Publicity, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Reza Daneshvar Personal and Business Correspondence, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Reza Daneshvar Creative Work, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Reza Daneshvar Publicity, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Sarah Mkhonza Personal and Business Correspondence, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Sarah Mkhonza Creative Work, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Sarah Mkhonza Publicity, 2006-2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Irakli Kakabadze Personal and Business Correspondence, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Irakli Kakabadze Creative Work, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Irakli Kakabadze Publicity, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Sonali Samarasinghe Creative Work, 2012-2014 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Sonali Samarasinghe Publicity, 2012-2014 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Voices of Freedom, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Voices of Freedom, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Voices of Freedom, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Voices of Freedom, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Voices of Freedom, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Voices of Freedom, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Voices of Freedom, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Voices of Freedom, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Voices of Freedom, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Exhibit labels and poster, 2016 (Box 1, Folder 33)